BLEACH EPISODE 45
Getsuga Tensho fused with Gran Rey Cero.
Born from the fusion of all things,
you are well-suited to this power.
But...
And yet... It still falls short!
DEFEND YOU
BLEACH: THOUSAND-YEAR BLOOD WAR
Brazo Izquierdo Del Diablo.
La Muerte!
Great!
Keep this up and defeat the rest of them!
What the heck?
- It's just you two?
- Where's Ichigo?
He and Inoue went after Yhwach.
Geez.
At least he didn't just charge off alone.
- Renji...
- Rukia, you go on ahead.
I'll handle things here.
Alright.
You don't seem to get it yet.
All of you are just stepping stones to me.
Uryu Ishida, is running away
all you can do?
Come on, nock your arrows,
the last Quincy.
I will cut down your arrows
and expose everything about you.
Bring it on, if your sword can reach me.
An unparalleled vortex of chaos.
This is
the power of the Soul King.
You can't stop it.
Shitenkoshun!
Ichigo, what is power?
What does it exist for?
You'd probably say, "to defend," right?
But that is a weak power.
True power is the one
that crushes everyone,
makes the world bow down,
and takes everything
in this world in hand.
Since you say you'll defeat me,
your power should be like this.
"To defend" is nothing but a lie.
Stop playing the hero,
Ichigo.
To defend...
I was trying to defend Kurosaki.
But my power is simply too weak.
If only my power were stronger...
A mere trifle.
I reject!
Reject!
Inoue!
Can you afford
to worry about someone else?
Fine, keep it up.
Until your power is exhausted.
I reject.
Inoue...
S... stop.
I reject.
- Enough, Inoue!
- Shut up.
I reject!
Did you exhaust your power on Ichigo?
But so what?
If only my power
were stronger...
You did well to hold on this long, Inoue.
Kuchiki.
Rukia?
Ichigo, I'm here to save you.
Inoue, are you alright?
Yeah.
Thank you for saving me.
Leave the rest to me.
It's been a while,
and you've changed quite a bit.
Wrapped up like a mummy
in a black blanket,
and you've even grown a horn.
Shut up.
I didn't ask to get wrapped up.
And the horn is cool, okay?
And what's your deal?
Don't just show up and start criticizing.
What did you say?
Is that how you talk to someone
who came to save you?
I didn't ask you to save me.
How could you even say that after being
wrapped like a mummy and beaten hard!
I was just about to counterattack!
Looks like you haven't backed down.
Of course not.
Rukia Kuchiki,
the Soul Reaper who guided Ichigo?
If I had to thank a Soul Reaper,
it would be you.
You're the one
who triggered Ichigo's awakening.
Then I don't need to apologize
for my rudeness.
The ones who will defeat you
will also be me and him.
- Rukia, let's go.
- Okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing new here.
One.
Two.
Three.
I see it.
The last Quincy is sneaking up
on someone with a sword.
It's an arrow.
Try predicting what I'm about to say too.
Grand Master!
If there is a next time.
What a pitiful sight.
But it suits you well, Uryu Ishida.
A fascinating power.
But fighting alongside your companions
has become a shackle instead.
Rukia, we need to go faster
and defeat that guy.
You don't have to tell me.
If only I had the power,
Kurosaki and Kuchiki
wouldn't have gotten hurt so badly.
It's all because my power is too weak.
That's why Kurosaki and Kuchiki
are suffering.
If only my power could become
stronger.
Return to nothing, you weaklings.
Farewell, my son.
It's the moon.
Ban...
kai.
So you're finally showing it?
Your Bankai.
Kurosaki.
I see.
So that is your Zangetsu.
For all the power you possess,
I will make it submit.
This power
is needed to protect everyone
from you.
Ichigo, you're too weak.
Yhwach, here I come.
What? My slash got slower?
But it's fine. I just need to wield it.
I definitely felt like I cut him.
Why are you still there?
What?
Detestable Spiritual Pressure!
So this is the power
that transcends Soul Reapers.
But I told you, you're too weak, Ichigo.
It feels as if the power is saying
it doesn't need companions.
Getsuga
Tensho!
Kurosaki.
"He's underestimating me."
"I'll defeat him in this instant."
That's what you were thinking, right?
I'm not underestimating you.
To consume you,
I must first know about you.
Ichigo, slash now! Right now!
And then, at that moment...
Getsuga!
It's over now!
Kurosaki.
You are the final onlooker.
I'll make you watch yourself
vanish from this world,
unable to protect anything,
leave nothing behind,
unable to do anything,
and end up being annihilated.
I will protect Kurosaki.
Your unwavering will is commendable,
but with your power,
let alone protecting Ichigo,
you are far from even qualified
to fight alongside him.
The reason you are here
is because Ichigo is too immature
to let go of his naivety.
Yhwach!
That woman has always been your weakness.
What hinders you from fighting
is precisely the reason
you hold your sword,
which is your heartfelt desire to protect.
It is because you fight
that you will be defeated.
Ichigo.
Bankai.
Hakka no Togame.
Getsuga
Tensho!
Kuchiki.
This is true power.
You are too foolish,
Ichigo.
This is the outcome of the protective
power you were talking about.
And this is the proof
of the mighty power I spoke of.
If only my power
could become stronger...
Be reduced to ashes, Uryu Ishida.
Just as I expected, Uryu Ishida.
Your trump card,
the Leiden Hant.
Come on, I've seen through
your next move too.
You'd better not use
His Majesty Yhwach's power
without restraint.
It'll leave you open.
Open?
Are you saying that because
you've already gotten behind me?
Shuno.
Tsubaki.
Ayame.
Hinagiku.
Baigon.
Lily.
Why am I so weak?
Why is my power so small?
Sternstaup!
I see it.
- Darn it!
- Three seconds.
If I look like I'm running around,
that's the reason for your defeat.
Once you use the Almighty,
you can't use that power again
within three seconds.
A mere three seconds
could never give you a chance to win.
But I still got three seconds.
If my power
were stronger than it is now,
so strong that even I couldn't bear it,
so vast and boundless...
If it could just envelop the entire world,
it would eliminate fighting, injury, pain,
and everything.
So I...
Are you sacrificing yourself,
Orihime Inoue?
This thing...
With this thing,
I can make your power disappear.
Wait.
Inoue!
Inoue...
BLEACH EPISODE 45
Bye-bye, Kurosaki.
I'll block it all for you.
DEFEND YOU
LIFE TO DEFEND YOU